hey guys what's up rob mods here
want to bring you another guide tonight
and something that
some people have been asking me about a
little bit over the last few days
and so i want to bring it up and
hopefully bring some clarity to it
so what i want to talk about is how to
progress as a new player
often especially you know at these later
stages of play
it's kind of difficult for me to like
both speak to really new players and
also still give insights to
players who've been around for a long
time and obviously i want to cater to
both but that's sometimes difficult to
do
so i'm doing my best to do that but
um just for for this one i want to talk
to newer players especially
and give my opinion of course this is
opinion and you can play however you
want but my opinion
on what i think is the best way for you
to progress in this game
and get ahead quickly so
let's get into it and um i'd love to
hear your feedback
and thoughts as to how to do this well
so
when you are first getting into the game
obviously
you your shop will be a whole lot
smaller than this one
so you're gonna start with only nine or
you know one ninth of this and you're
only going to have a couple furniture
slots and that sort of thing and
so this is basically a mac shop this is
what you know it's gonna look like
super super late game
but when you're first starting out of
course there's a few mistakes
that you can make and i'm gonna go into
that in later videos but for this one
i really just wanted to focus on how to
progress well and we'll talk about
common mistakes and how to
fix those later on so first things first
i would say
for your first couple of weeks of play
just enjoy the game just
get into it play it enjoy it and um
don't stress too much your first couple
weeks is just going to be getting used
to how it plays how it feels
um all the different aspects of the game
you know i can make a video every day
for 100 days and still not touch
every thing that i i think about and
that i've contemplated
so yeah don't worry about that too much
i would say just enjoy the game and and
i think your focus for the first little
bit
is just to master like tier four
or five like just master everything in
the first few tiers
uh see what you what you know
you enjoy crafting um what it actually
looks like the first
few tiers they're quick they're easy
they're enjoyable
and you know it's not going to take you
forever and ever just to master anything
it's going to come pretty quickly
next thing is that i would say it's
really important
at the beginning to just balance
between racks and bins
sometimes you want to really lean one
way or the other but i think it is
really important just to balance between
the two
because racks is really important for
you to be able to speed up crafts for
your small talks to be bigger so that
you can suggest other items
and and rush things and sell things and
make money that way
but bins is going to be really important
because you're not going to get very far
if you're not crafting anything that's
going to be your main money maker
so balancing between those two honestly
it takes about a day to get anything up
to level seven or eight
so if you just focused on one a day and
you had the money for it
you can get everything in your shop up
to level seven or eight
one a day and it would take you a couple
weeks basically to get everything up to
a level that's
decent and you can be moving forward
with your shop
i would say that's priority i would say
at the start don't spend any gems don't
spend any ascension shards
don't spend much of anything on your
heroes mainly because
the further tiers of heroes aren't going
to be unlocked yet you're not going to
be able to spend the money on them
like five mil or 10 mil each or whatever
they are at the last tier
so don't worry about that so much i mean
eventually you're going to be re-rolling
for higher level heroes better heroes
and you don't get
anything when you retire a hero you
literally do not get anything extra
you just have to start from ground zero
and so for you to be investing anything
major into your heroes right now doesn't
make a whole lot of sense
i mean sure you're going to want to be
doing quests and getting components and
using it to craft and that sort of thing
of course but i would say don't go out
of your way to spend a whole lot
on that i probably shouldn't play at the
same time because
it's harder to talk and play
intentionally at the same time so
the next thing i would say is there's
certain things that are going to get you
ahead a lot faster than others a lot of
people will
ask the question like should i be
expanding my shop should i be
spending gems to to rush different
things or whatever
and so i would say your pro top priority
for the first little bit
is to spend your gems on expanding your
shop
and crafting slots those are your two
main things those are your priority
when you're when your shop is expanded
you have more furniture slots you can
get more things up to level seven and
eight so that's gonna
create a really good foundation for at
least your gameplay
and then when you can open up crafting
slots obviously you're making more items
at a time you're able to make more money
um and it just makes a whole lot more
sense so those are your priorities
expand your shop get crafting slots
balance between bins and racks and just
try to expand and move forward
i would say once you've mastered tier
four and five and you're looking into
okay what do i want to do next how do i
actually like get ahead in this game
it is competitive there's a lot of
players that are around that level
trying to get ahead
and so you're going to have to be smart
about it what i would
say is look at the video when i talk
about choosing lines and
and crafting and choose really
specifically which lines that you're
going to choose
you can look in ascensions over here
sorry i should have shown you
where that is you can look up here in
your in your profile
and you can click on ascensions right
here and you can see
[Music]
how many stars that you put in each one
so i would say choose
four that you're gonna you're gonna
stick with
and those will be your regular rotation
make sure you check out the crafting
video so that you're not overlapping
resources and stuff make sure that it
makes sense for you
choose those four and i would say really
focused on them
let's say you have um four
craftings or eight crafting slots open
you've got four different items that
you're crafting
i would say your goal should be to get
your bins to the point that you can
start eight items simultaneously as soon
as you log in so you're
able to just log in craft eight items
you're rolling
and and you can go from there and then
you can start upgrading
your racks and getting your max energy
up i think that's going to make the most
sense for you
and as you your bins increase and as
your tier increases
you can go from tier 6 to tier 7 to tier
focusing on those four items and as your
shop expands as you have more energy as
you know you progress in the game it'll
get easier and easier to master the
other things but that i don't think
shouldn't be the focus if you actually
want to get ahead
definitely i would say your focus needs
to be long-term it's not on short-term
goals it's not on
oh i just need to like get the highest
level of this dungeon eventually every
dungeon's gonna hit max you're just
gonna be fighting bosses to get keys
anyway so
don't focus on those little things focus
long term
focus on getting to a higher tier of
item crafting a higher tier of item
making money expanding your shop
getting more of your crafting slots
and that's going to be your best bet for
starting off
also i mean sure some of these videos
may be
you know above your understanding at
this point being a newer player and
that's totally fine but watching other
videos
trying to learn how top players do it
and
at least you know changing your gameplay
around so that you're
trying to at least improve that's going
to help you
absolutely a ton last thing i want to
mention is this
guild is incredibly important it's very
very important
so if you're in a guild that's a lower
level you're getting towards the top
they're not that active they're not
progressive
i would say go out of your way to find a
really good guild
when when you get a guild that has
really high level buildings
everything's crafting literally twice as
fast you've got
resources coming in incredibly fast i
mean if you look at this
we've got we've got these bonuses right
here
where everything crafts 25 faster
and i get resources 50 percent faster so
i'm able to craft
things incredibly quickly just because
of guild bonuses
if you look here at my workers
workers everything that's available to
me
crafts at 51 speed except for the one
girl
so that means that all of my stuff
crafts twice as fast as usual
plus the crafting bonus so all of my
stuff crafts so quickly plus i'm getting
a ton of resources
plus the town hall is a really high
level my heroes are all able to get up
to level 40 39 39 40 40 40 40.
so having higher level heroes having
different things available
so for you to get in a progressive guild
that's finishing off bounties that's
getting bonuses that's able to implement
these sort of things get high level
buildings
that's going to help you a ton so if you
focus on those things get in a quality
guild it should help you to move forward
again as always if you guys have any
questions or
anything specific ideas for videos or
want to reach out to me please feel free
to do so i love to chat about this kind
of stuff
and help you out the best that i can i
hope you're enjoying it
and yeah thank you so much for watching
i really do appreciate it
have a great night and we'll talk to you
soon